Oh, no!
You've done it now, Kugisaki.
This was Gojo-sensei's, right?
Ijichi-san.
Between Ijichi-san, who left us in
charge of this freshly cleaned shirt,
Me ♥
and me, who spilled coffee on it...
Who's more at fault?
You.
You pat it down, pat it down.
I'm working on it!
It kind of looks like a marimekko.
Don't take apparel so lightly.
Eh, I'm sure it's a cheap shirt, anyway.
Fushiguro, look up the brand on the tag.
A-After tax?
Before tax.
Is that even important?
We have no choice.
I'll put in 90,000.
You can each put in 80,000.
Huh?!
Morning!
Ijichi said you guys had my shirt?
What's the matter, Megumi?
Nothing.
Kugisaki...
I-I can't...
I'm thrilled!
By my own talent!
Ah, I really am...
I truly am...
a curse!
Black Flash!
I bet you just thought
this would be some pest extermination,
or like defeating evil spirits in a legend,
or something like that
when you came here, right?!
You're naïve! You damn brat!
This is war!
It's not some fight to correct a mistake!
It's a clash of what we believe is right!
Of our own flimsy ideas of justice!
You are me, Yuji Itadori.
Just as I kill people
without a second thought,
you save people without a second thought!
It's our instincts
versus the dignity
gained by human reasoning!
This is a war to determine which of those
will be left standing a century from now!
If you haven't even realized that yet,
how are you supposed to beat me?
Hey, Yuji Itadori.
Have you counted how
many curses you've killed?
I bet not.
Me, neither!
I really couldn't care less about
the number of humans I've killed.
Eventually, I'll forget all about you, too.
The bells of the Gion monastery in India
echo with the warning that
all things are impermanent.
The blossoms of the sala trees
teach us through their hues
that what flourishes must fade.
However!
We are the exception!
Episode 44
Right and Wrong, Part 3
JUJUTSU KAISEN
Shibuya Incident
23:09            Tokyo Metro, Shibuya Station
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hFloor B5, Shin-toshin Line Platform
These people...
Kyoto School First-Year, Arata Nitta
are alive, right?
It looks like Suguru Geto has
already left with the Prison Realm.
No way!
Let's switch gears.
Our goal has changed from
fighting to reclaim Satoru Gojo
to fighting to save our allies and shave away
as much of the enemy forces as possible,
starting right now!
Let's hurry.
My brother should already be nearby.
He has a brother?
I could have sworn he was an only child.
What just happened?
A face with a scar!
Plus the way he switched places just now!
Is he the sorcerer who
drove Hanami into a corner?!
Todo-san!
I finished treating that girl over there.
She's probably dead, though.
So please don't blame me later!
Enough prattle.
See to my brother, too.
Wake up, Brother!
Our battle has just begun!
Talk about ominous lines!
Todo...
I...
can't...
fight anymore!
It wasn't just Kugisaki...
Nanamin died, too.
Sukuna... killed so many.
So I have to save...
that many more people...
But I couldn't!
I'm just a murderer!
What I thought was my conviction
was just an excuse I made for myself!
I can't...
forgive myself anymore.
Speak up! I can't hear you!
Amazing!
Even when you know about it,
it's still this disorienting?!
Brother...
A man as great as you shouldn't
let yourself grow so small.
We are jujutsu sorcerers.
Me,
you,
Kugisaki,
Mr. Nanami,
and all of our allies are jujutsu sorcerers!
So long as we continue to live,
our dead comrades
have not truly been defeated!
This is not a matter of sins
and punishments.
The moment we chose to
live as jujutsu sorcerers,
our lives were no longer
bound by such karma.
Attempting to find meaning
in the deaths of the fallen
can, at times, defile the
memories of those we've lost!
But even so!
What have they entrusted you with?
There's no need to find
your answer to that now.
But until you do,
you cannot stop moving forward.
That is the one punishment imposed
on those who live as jujutsu sorcerers.
There's no need to tell my brother
about that right now.
I've applied my technique to you.
Now, listen up, Itadori-kun.
The wounds you have suffered
so far will no longer worsen.
They are not healed,
but you'll stop losing blood,
and it should take the edge off the pain.
But that only applies
to your current wounds.
If you take another attack,
you'll be further wounded,
and my technique won't apply to those.
Todo-san's little brother
doesn't resemble him at all.
I gave the girl over there
the same treatment.
She didn't have a pulse
and wasn't breathing,
but it hadn't been very long.
The chance that she survives isn't zero.
I'm taking her with me
and getting out of here.
I'm just saying the chance isn't zero!
Please don't get your hopes up too high!
Yeah...
Yeah!
Are you finished talking, topknot gorilla?
What's wrong?
You won't touch me?
He's skilled.
He's parrying me while also keeping
distance from the nearly finished Itadori.
That's not all I've got.
He dodged it?
Bring on the switch!
This time, I'll adapt!
I'll hit him for sure!
I want to land that thing once more!
I can feel myself close to reaching it!
The true essence of my soul!
I'm sorry, Nanamin.
I was trying to take the easy way out.
I even used my sins as an excuse to run away.
Please take it from here.
Black Flash!
I'll make sure I take on your
share of suffering, too, Nanamin.
Tsk! Half-dead boy!
Welcome back.
Yeah!
Shibuya Station Closed Off
Matters should be settled already.
There's no point in going to Shibuya now.
Head back, Miwa.
Why only Todo-senpai and Nitta-kun?
I reasoned there's a 99% chance
that Todo won't die in Shibuya.
Same for Nitta if he accompanied Todo.
His technique would be useful, too—
And me?!
Am I useless?
The situation isn't even
on that scale anymore.
It wasn't just you.
It was Mai, Kamo, Nishimiya,
and Utahime, too.
I took steps to make sure you all were
on a mission south of Kyoto on the 31st.
Why didn't you say anything to us?
Why didn't you ask us for help?
Aren't we friends?
Is it because...
I'm weak?
No. I'm the one who was weak.
I went about it the wrong way
because I was weak,
and I couldn't even see that mistake
through because I was weak.
There was this girl I loved.
And I didn't care what
happened to the world
as long as I could be at
her side and protect her.
Even if that girl didn't want me
to be the one to protect her.
Time's up, Miwa.
No!
Goodbye. Thank you—
Don't say goodbye!
Miwa.
Mechamaru!
Miwa!
Please find happiness.
Whatever shape it takes,
as long as you're happy,
my wish has come true.
Mechamaru...
Utahime-sensei, what Mechamaru did...
Will go unquestioned.
The man is dead, after all.
He held us in awfully low regard, huh?
Right?
And this whole "Todo-kun wouldn't die" crap?
Is he saying that we would die, then?
I'll murder whoever
makes my cute junior cry.
He can switch positions
with inanimate objects?!
He split apart!
Soul Multiplicity!
Body Repel!
Topknot Gorilla's soul is
still at full strength,
but could I kill him with
one touch in my current state?
Itadori's soul is down to about 10% left.
And my soul is down to 40%.
Having my double crushed
and eating Itadori's rush of
Black Flashes shaved away an awful lot.
And that's all thanks to that woman.
She was a nobody, but she
still left her damn mark behind.
I'll start by eliminating
this annoying switcher first!
Brother!
If you're satisfied with
staying on that level,
you and I won't stay best friends.
This cursed spirit is already
landing Black Flash, too...
I'm the one being left behind right now.
You've grown strong, Brother.
Are you satisfied with that,
Aoi Todo?!
Are you planning to leave
your brother alone once again,
Aoi Todo?!
Tan-taka-tan!
Black Flash!
It doesn't matter how
powerful your attack is,
or if you throw out a Black Flash.
Your attacks don't affect my soul,
so they're pointless.
However, with that,
all three of them were now...
Smooch!
Smooch♥
...drawing out 120% of their latent potential.
Soul Multiplicity!
Body Repel!
An omnidirectional attack
that makes switching pointless!
He's getting into high gear!
Let's kick it up a notch, Itadori!
This will be the last time
you and I curse each other!
They say a hero always arrives late,
but everyone understands
that those who worked hard
and held out are heroes, too, right?
Next time, "Metamorphosis."
Next Episode
Metamorphosis
Don't forget to grab your delay certificate!